

CONTACT

- (a) (+84) 368202485
- anhuc.forwork@gmail.com
- 🩎 Ha Noi, Viet Nam <u>115000</u>

SUMMARY

As a sophomore majoring in Digital Marketing, I always want to have opportunities to gain more experience in the fields of Economics and Business. I'm very excited to develop soft skills to adapt and keep up with the times.

I have also been active in one of the biggest clubs of NEU -Economists Club, Young considered which miniature business. Here, I have experienced leadership positions as an Department member and developed soft skills such as leadership, teamwork, critical time thinking and management.

Ung Chau Anh

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

November 2023 - January 2024

Marketing Collaborator at One Mount

- Participate in developing and implementing market research activities, competitors, and customers for the fields of Retail distribution, FMCG industry.
- Analyze and process collected information to provide comparisons, instructions, and detailed information

December 2022 - October 2023

Member of Event Department of YEC (NEU).

- Leader of Event Department at Hanh Trinh Kinh Doanh 2023.
 - General management and direction during Talkshows and Webinars with nearly 1,000 participants.
 - Oversee the program committee's planning and preparations.
 - Take part in the Management Team for Competition Media Ambassadors.
- Leader of events in the workshop series "Mentoring Series 2023", and internal activities series "Nhat Ky YEC 2023".
 - Build workflow and manage overview for live Webinar sessions with about 500 participants.
 - Work directly with program partners.

December 2022 - January 2023

Co-Founder of Hoa Land

- Research customers and markets to develop products at Hoa Land.
- Media manager, responsible for designing publications and posts on the page.

July 2022 - September 2022

Marketing Assistant at Elite Academy

• Manage an academic page for an English centre. Reached more than 1 thousand followers in 1 month.

EDUCATION

2022 - Now

National Economics University

· Majoring in Digital Marketing

LANGUAGES

- Vietnamese: First Language
- English: C1

Advanced

• IELTS Band Score: 7.0

SKILLS

- · Computer: Microsoft Powerpoint, Excel, Word
- Basic Design Skills
- Leadership
- · Creative Thinking
- Public Speaking